<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Arvey R. Jimenez Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://Arvey18.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://Arvey18.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-04-21T13:08:51+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://Arvey18.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Arvey Jimenez]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Other Effects of Image Slider]]></title>
    <link href="http://Arvey18.github.io/blog/2014/04/14/exercise2/"/>
    <updated>2014-04-14T09:39:51+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://Arvey18.github.io/blog/2014/04/14/exercise2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p align = "justify " style = "text-indent: 30px;">This is one of my favorite image slider that ive done so far. Showing 3 images and when clicked left and right, it will show the other image  grouped into 3 again. I also learned some other effects inside image slider like the putting some description and adding some animation on it. Output below.</p>


<p><img class="left" src="http://Arvey18.github.io/images/Exercise2.png" title="image" alt="images"></p>

<p><em>&mdash;Home Page</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Javascript and Jquery]]></title>
    <link href="http://Arvey18.github.io/blog/2014/04/08/learning-javascript-and-jquery/"/>
    <updated>2014-04-08T10:42:59+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://Arvey18.github.io/blog/2014/04/08/learning-javascript-and-jquery</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p align = "justify " style = "text-indent: 30px;"> Learning Javascript and Jquery is not easy for me, because in school we dont have a subject for Javascript and Jquery. Javascript and Jquery enables you to make different effects on a website. You can do some animation like an image slider that will slide or fade, you can do also some effect like when you click the button there will a message or picture that will pop-out. There are so many thing you can do using Javascript or Jquery.</p>




<h3> Difference Between The Two </h3>




<h4><em> Javascript </em> </h4>


<p align = "justify " style = "text-indent: 30px;"> Javascript is a scripting language developed by Netscape to enable Web authors to design interactive sites. Javascript is different from Java. Sample code below.</p>


<p><img class="left" src="http://Arvey18.github.io/images/Javascript.png" title="image" alt="images"></p>

<h4><em> Jquery </em> </h4>


<p align = "justify " style = "text-indent: 30px;"> Jquery for me is much easy than the Javascript and much flexible, because you can do much more and much easy with the use of Javascript. The only difference between them i think is the code but same function. Sample code below.</p>


<p><img class="left" src="http://Arvey18.github.io/images/Jquery.png" title="image" alt="images"></p>

<!--more-->


<h3> First Exercise in FavMed using Javascript and Jquery (Simple Image Slider).</h3>


<p><img class="left" src="http://Arvey18.github.io/images/Exercise1.png" title="image" alt="images"></p>

<h5><em>&#8212;Home Page</em></h5>



]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Post]]></title>
    <link href="http://Arvey18.github.io/blog/2014/03/31/first-post/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-31T09:49:19+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://Arvey18.github.io/blog/2014/03/31/first-post</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p align = "justify" style = "text-indent: 30px;"> First of all. My name is Arvey R. Jimenez, 20 years old. I&#8217;m a 4th year BSIT Student at Nueva Ecija University of Science and Technology (NEUST). I will graduate this coming April 3, 2014 and this is how i got here at Favorite Medium as a trainee.</p>


<p align = "justify" style = "text-indent: 30px;">First, there was a event in our deparment CICT, titled &#8220;TECHNO DAY&#8221; and there are a lot of contest like Java Programming, Networking, Typing, Quiz bee and the contest that i joined was the Web Design and i really don&#8217;t expect that i will win that contest but thanks to God i won. In the awarding ceremony we have a guest named Mr. Efren Lim and they said he also graduated at NEUST and now a successful Web Developer. I didn&#8217;t expect anything when they said it and after the awarding Mr. Lim invited me with my other classmate to go to his office. The day he said that, i really thank god for giving us an oppurtunity like this. The day that we are there, he said they are looking for trainee to work for thier company and we need to pass it. When he said that, we already grab the oppurtunity and will do our best. I am really happy on that day and thanks to Favorite Medium for giving us an oppurtunity. That&#8217;s how i became a trainee here at Favorite Medium together with my classmates. This is one of the best gift I received before my graduation. Hopefully i passed the training and get my 1st job as a Web Developer at Favorite Medium. </p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
